{
	"questions": [
		{
			"question": "What are dart defines used for in Flutter?",
			"answers": [
				"To store compile-time constants without hardcoding them in the source code",
				"To store compile-time constants that affect your Dart code only",
				"To store compile-time constants that affect both your Dart code and native platform code",
				"To securely store encrypted data on device"
			],
			"correct": [1, 2]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which mixin is used to synchronize the UI with the refresh rate of the device?",
			"answers": [
				"AutomaticKeepAliveClientMixin",
				"SingleTickerProviderStateMixin",
				"ViewportElementMixin",
				"RestorationMixin"
			],
			"correct": [2]
		},    
		{
			"question": "What are common usages of the BuildContext in Flutter?",
			"answers": [
				"To access ancestor widgets in the widget tree",
				"To store build configuration settings",
				"To access localizations strings for the current locale",
				"To handle platform-specific code"
			],
			"correct": [1,3]
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the mounted property?",
			"answers": [
				"To check if a widget has been initialized",
				"To check if a widget has state",
				"To check if a widget is visible",
				"To check if a widget is currently in the widget tree"
			],
			"correct": [4]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which widgets should you use to create a scrollable collection of items?",
			"answers": [
				"Column",
				"ListView",
				"Stack",
				"GridView"
			],
			"correct": [2,4]
		},
		{
			"question": "When should you use the required keyword in a function parameter list?",
			"answers": [
				"For positional non-nullable parameters",
				"For named non-nullable parameters with a default value",
				"For named non-nullable parameters without a default value",
				"For constant parameters"
			],
			"correct": [3]
		},    
		{
			"question": "Which of the following statements are true about StatelessWidget and StatefulWidget?",
			"answers": [
				"StatelessWidget doesn't have a setState method",
				"StatefulWidget rebuilds itself and all descendant widgets when its state changes",
				"StatefulWidget holds mutable state within its State object",
				"StatelessWidget only ever rebuilds when its parent is rebuilt"
			],
			"correct": [1,3]
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the didUpdateWidget() method?",
			"answers": [
				"To initialize the widget",
				"To respond to widget configuration changes",
				"To rebuild the widget",
				"To dispose of resources"
			],
			"correct": [2]
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the analysis_options.yaml file?",
			"answers": [
				"To define the code generation order",
				"To enable/disable linter rules",
				"To enable experimental analyzer plugins",
				"To define the packages used in the project"
			],
			"correct": [2,3]
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the difference between debugPrint() and print()?",
			"answers": [
				"print is only available in debug mode",
				"debugPrint is only available in release mode",
				"debugPrint throttles output to prevent lag",
				"There is no difference"
			],
			"correct": [3]
		}
	]
}

